What's going on...?
Jeez, why didn't you wake me up sooner?
I don't have time to make your lunch.
Well, that ship has sailed...
Has anyone seen my underwear?
Whoa, Elfuda-san!
Please put on some clothes!
"Elfuda-san"?
What are we, business associates?
Just call me El like you normally do.
Huh?
You're acting strange.
Are you running a fever?
K..Kuroeda-san! What are you doing?!
You don't feel warm to me.
Also... my name's Khloe.
Now hurry up or else
we'll be late for school.
Calorie Lovers
Proudly presenting the flab-ulous new rom-com!!
"Calorie Lovers"!
Plus-Sized Elf
I swear, this morning has been
full of surprises...
Khloe Kuroeda
Naoe Tomoatsu
El Elfuda
You can say that again.
Calorie Lovers
For a minute there,
I thought you'd forgotten all about us.
Didn't get enough sleep?
We promised your mom
we'd keep an eye on you
while she's away for work, remember?
Yeah, I remember.
But crawling into my bed is a bit much...
W-we just don't want you
to catch a cold, Tomo-kun.
If you get sick while we're house-sitting,
your mother will be upset with us.
Yeah, but we're not kids anymore...
Ooh, you feeling frisky?
Wh-what...?!
Ugh, don't be gross.
There's no reason to start acting
all shy around us.
We've been friends since kindergarten.
I get that, but-
Since kindergarten...?
What's wrong?
I just... feel a little off today.
G'morning!
Hey, don't do that!
Hey, cut it out!
Melody Mero
Good morning!
Hana Kusahanada
Iberiko Oku
Kotsue Honeda
Good morning, ladies.
"Ladies"? Why so formal?
It's weird hearing you
talk like that, Tomo-kun.
Huh?
Oh, uh, gotcha...
Tomo-kun, you're so funny.
We're late! We're late!
C-can't stop now!
Laika Raika
Pure Satero
Outta the way!
Ai Hitome
Drako Gonda
Stop looking up our skirts!
Wait a second... Tomo-kun, is that you?
How many times have I told you
to watch where you're walking?
Well, at any rate, it looks like
the kindergarten gang's all here.
That's like... an entire class...
Speakin' of which,
the two of you totally cheated!
Gulp...
I knew it.
Don't give us that "gulp" nonsense!
Today was supposed to be the day we decide
who's staying at Tomo-chan's place...
It's not fair that you live
in the same neighborhood!
Yeah, what she said!
I wanna sleep with Tomo-kun, too!
Me, too!
And me...
Laika, too.
Calm down, ladies-
Crap, we're late!
Run for it!
O-okay!
Hey, get back here!
So sleepy...
Oh, come on!
Jeez, I looked away for like five seconds!
That's kind of hypocritical, don't you think?
Yeah, what she said!
You're the one who went
breakin' the rules first!
Everyone gets equal time with Tomo-kun.
That's the rule!
Why are they hovering around my desk...?
Knock it off and go sit down, all of you.
Class President
Sensei's going to be here any minute.
Besides, you're bothering Tomo-kun.
Fine...
Thanks, I appreciate it.
N-no problem.
It's my job as class president.
Morning.
Good morning, Oeda-sensei!
Hyoka Oeda
Morning, Tomo-kun.
G-good morning...
Now, why don't we skip straight to
homeroom, just you and me?
HEY!
That's inappropriate, Auntie!
Preying on innocent students?!
What's wrong with you?!
I don't get to walk to school
with Tomo-kun,
so I'm entitled to make up for lost time.
Yeah, but we aren't spending
any one-on-one time with him!
Sh-she's got a point!
The rest of us are waiting our turn!
This is an abuse of power!
Whoa, take it easy!
We're supposed to be getting ready
for first period to start!
If you say so, Tomo-kun...
Whew, it's been a long day...
Why's everyone so obsessed with me...?
M-my bad! Are you okay?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
I-I'm sorry!
Oh, I know!
Wouldn't want you catching a cold.
You can wear my jacket.
It might smell kind of bad though.
Tomo-chan...
I don't think it smells bad.
It smells like you.
SERIOUSLY?!
This hottie looks good all wet, don'tcha think?
See-through!
Tomo-kun, I get to borrow
your jacket too, right?
A-and me...
They're acting weird...
There, there... Good doggie.
Eat your fill.
I have more, so there's
no need to scarf it down.
You've got a soft side, Miss President.
T..Tomo-kun?!
Feeding a stray puppy, I mean.
N-not really...
It just reminded me of you,
all uncoordinated and awkward...
Really?
Then do I get a treat, too?
Sure. Here, want a piece of jerky?
Mhm, thanks.
T..Tomo-kun...
Miss President?
HEY! What are you two
sneaking around back there for?!
Something's definitely not right...
Why not eat in the counseling office?
Because he's eating with me
on the rooftop today.
Oh? But that's supposed to be my job.
Open wide and I'll feed you!
Th-that's not fair! What about me?
Laika, too!
I-I can't take it anymore!
Tomo-kun...?
Wh-what's the matter?
This whole situation seems
WAY too good to be true...
Why are all of you so hell-bent on
being alone with me anyway?
Tomo-kun, what's going on with you?
You already know the answer to that!
It's because we're all in love with you.
Love!
Wh-what?!
What kind of a reaction is that?
You're behaving strangely today.
Wait a minute...
You haven't forgotten your promise, have you?
Uh, promise...?
The promise you made when we were kids!
You said you'd marry whichever one of us
pudgy girls was your favorite!
I-I said that...?
You jerk! Don't act like you're not
Mr. Chubby Chaser!
Tomo-kun...
Surely you aren't trying to
weasel your way out
by pretending to forget just because
you're inconvenienced by us...
Hold on! I swear I didn't-
So THAT'S your game...
It's too late to go back on your word...
FREEZE-
-suckers!
Tomo-kun is betrothed to his mommy!
Papa!
He proposed to me with a flower
when he was just a tiny thing!
Parents aren't allowed to marry
their own children!
What happened to your business trip...?
And why'd you bust in through the window...?
Oh, that reminds me!
We need to evacuate, quickly!
Evacuate...?
While you were busy starring in
a romantic comedy,
something terrible happened
to the rest of the world!
What the...?!
What's going on down there?!
Are they EATING people?!
A new diet supplement
appeared on the market recently...
Anyone who takes the supplement
to lose weight...
Calories...!
...turns into a zombie!
Fats...!
Carbs...!
Fats...! Carbs...!
CALORIES...!
HEEEEELP!
Calories of the Dead
What in the world...?
Calories...
That's odd. Why's he having a nightmare?
He was supposed to move straight into
the "fat and happy" stage
right after the harem plot twist...
Targeting the human again?
Haven't you learned your lesson?
The dark elf?! What are you doing here?!
Disguising your spell was clever,
I'll admit.
Unfortunately for you,
I'm not falling for it.
So YOU did this...
Calories...
I already called dibs on the human!
Keep your hands off!
I'm afraid I can't do that.
If the human gets fat, he'll be
too worried about his own health
to focus on keeping the rest of us in line.
Wow, talk about a selfish attitude!
Well, if you INSIST on getting in my way...
It's too late.
You walked right into the magical trap I set!
Crap-!
Why, you...!
Imagine!
A counter-nightmare?!
A mana explosion?!
NOOOOO!
The hell happened...?